# **Bhavesh Shahani**

## JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

Indore,India.

gudd.shahani@gmail.com

in BhaveshShahani\_LinkedIn

BhaveshShahani\_Github

▶ BhaveshShahani\_Portfolio



#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMERY**

Software Developer with knowledge of web development technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Able to learn new technologies and software. Have an experience of 1000+ hours of Coding and Data Structure Algorithms. Team player who provides valuable support in a team environment.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Full Stack Web Developer**

*Masai School*Apr 2022 – present | Bangalore

#### 12th

Sanmati School May 2016 | Indore

#### 10th

CDS School 2014 | Nagpur

## **CERTIFICATES**

• Diploma In Event Managment.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JAVA | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS | DSA

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Work | Problem Solving | Motivated

#### **INTERESTS**

Travelling | Hiking | Cooking

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Store Manager**

*Mithi Mirchi Cafe* 2019 – 2020 | Indore Worked as a Store Manager.

#### **Sales Manager**

*DAYA WorldWide PVT. LTD.*2017 – 2019 | Indore
Worked as a Sales Manager.

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Bewakoof Clone**

Bewakoof is a lifestyle fashion brand that makes creative, distinctive fashion for the trendy, contemporary Indian, with the help of 4 members made a clone of Bewakoof.com.

#### **Tech-Stack**

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.

#### Responsibility

- Product Page Design.
- Sorting.

\_\_\_\_\_

## **Bath And Body Works Clone**

Bath & Body Work is an online eCommerce cosmetic brand, Which is a retail store chain that sells soaps, lotions, fragrances, and candles. We with the help of 4 members tried to clone the website.

## **Tech-Stack**

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.

## Responsibility

- Team Lead
- Layout of the website
- Merging

\_\_\_\_\_